<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="help_line_1">Agenda View</string>
    <string name="help_line_2">
        Use the Agenda View to view all your events. Click
        on an event to view the details of that event. Long click on an
        event to delete that event, or to delete multiple events. Add an event by
        clicking the New Event icon in the action bar.
        
    </string>
    
    <string name="help_line_3">Weekly View</string>
    <string name="help_line_4">
        Use the Weekly View to view all your events for the current week. Clicking on 
        a particular day will bring up the New Event screen with the date
        auto filled to the day clicked. Like in the Agenda View, add an
        event by clicking the New Event icon in the action bar.
    </string>
    
    <string name="help_line_5">New Event View</string>
    <string name="help_line_6">
        Use the New Event screen to add an event. Events must have a title,
        date, start time, and end time. Add an attendee to an event
        by clicking the Add Person icon in the action bar, which will allow
        you to select a person from your contacts. Only contacts with
        email addresses can be added. Save the event by clicking the
        Save Event icon in the action bar.  
    </string>
    
    <string name="help_line_7">View Event View</string>
    <string name="help_line_8">
        Use the View Event screen to view the details of an event. Delete the
        event by clicking the Delete Event icon in the action bar. Edit the
        event by clicking the Edit Event icon in the action bar. 
    </string>
    
    <string name="help_line_9">Edit Event View</string>
    <string name="help_line_10">
        Use the Edit Event screen to edit an event. Add an attendee to an event
        by clicking the Add Person icon in the action bar. Save the event by
        clicking the Save Event icon in the action bar. 
    </string>
    
    
</resources>
